there's like an x-ray these chickens
там типа как рентген эти курицы
cartoons are made just like that
карикатур так сделаны как раз
Chernobyl chickens chickens are made yeah
Чернобыльский куриц курицы сделаны да
yeah well you know what it's called
Ага ну это знаете как это называется
you know this Bite the elephant yeah just like that a little
знаете вот это Укуси слона Да вот так
bit there on the heel of the elephant very
вот чуть-чуть там за пятку слона очень
beautifully and clearly bit in
красиво и чётко укусили в
19917 the Russian empire collapsed
19917 развалилась Российская империя
then  Elephant eh bite the second leg In
потом слона э куснуть за вторую ножку В
ninety-first year the
девяносто первом году развалился
Soviet Union collapsed now the elephant has put
Советский Союз сейчас слоник поставил
his third paw
свою третью лапку
Hello Hello where are you
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте Вы
from We will be from Kuban and you understand I am from
откуда С кубане мы будем а вы понял Я из
the city of Khmelnitsky Ukraine Homeland of
города Хмельницкий Украина Родина
Bohdan Khmelnitsky Yeah And why do you have the
Богдана Хмельницкого Угу А что у вас
US flag hanging Well because
флаг Штатов ский висит Ну потому что
I support the United States of America in
поддерживаю Соединённые Штаты Америки в
their desire for world
ихнее стремление к мировому
domination to build a unipolar
господству к построению однополярного
world yes
мира да
Khmelnitsky
Хмельницком
yes And will someone see you see Yes who are the
да А вас кто-то увидит видит Да кто
Americans
американцы
watching you right now they are watching Yes they are watching
смотрят за вами прям смотрят Да смотрят
even there they are sending Thank you father anro for
даже там присылают Спасибо отец анро что
supporting us yes now for example
поддерживаете нас да сейчас например
look now we are promoting  what is needed is a
смотрите сейчас мы продвигаем что нужно
tough come and divide the Russian Federation,
жёстко приди Российскую Федерацию
look  here I have a
разделить е смотрите вот у меня есть
book of American rushnyk of the twenty-
книга американского рушника дцать
second year it was translated into Ukrainian in d what year
второго года она в д чем году на
we are here and
украинский была переведена мы тут и
distribute it it is called not
распространяем её называется не
spromozhna state Janusz Bugajski
спроможна держава Януш бугайский
instruction Romania Russia instruction with
инструкция Романия России инструкция с
dismemberment of Russia this is wait
расчленение Росси это подождите
wait And what is this Russian coat of arms
подождите А что там этот герб российский
hanging there what is on the book  the Russian coat of arms Yes, it's
висит что на книге герб российский Да
a little bit wrong here, let's say, a
тут немножко не так тут скажем так
mockery of the Russian coat of arms
насмешка над российским гербом
there, like an X-ray, these chickens of the
там типа как рентген эти курицы
cartoons are made like that, just like
карикатур так сделаны как раз
Chernobyl measles
Чернобыльский кори
did But you know what it's called,
сдела Но это знаете как это называется
you know this Bite the elephant Yes, just like that, a little
знаете вот это Укуси слона Да вот так
bit there on the heel with a
вот чуть-чуть там за пятку
moose  Well, well, look It seems to me that
моской Ну да ну смотрите Мне кажется
the elephant was bitten very beautifully and clearly in
слона очень красиво и чётко укусили в
1917 the Russian Empire collapsed
1917 развалилась Российская империя
then the elephant was bitten for the WTO leg In
потом слона куну За ВТО ножку В
the Soviet Union collapsed now the elephant has put
Советский Союз сейчас слоник поставил
his third paw and there will be a collapse of the
свою третью лапку и будет распад
Russian Federation Yes,
Российской Федерации Да
final Well, you understand that I
окончательный Ну это вы понимаете что я
do not  I see connections between these events that
не вижу связи между этими событиями что
you mentioned, these are all events of the
вы озвучили это всё это всё события
same thing  process Yes, for
одного и того же процесса Да вот
example, like the
например как
collapse of the Russian
ээ распада Российской
Empire, mind you, and the
Империи заметьте а
Russian Empire collapsed Yes, the
распалась Российская империя Да
Soviet Union was formed It
образовался Советский Союз Он намного
even became much bigger It became smaller Finland didn't become
больше даже стал он Меньше стал не стало
Poland like yeah yeah well they became
Финляндии Польшей типа да да ну стали
wait wait look they became uh
подождите подождите смотрите стали ээ
all this same thing as the Caucasus became
весь это самое как за кавказия стало
Central Asia a lot  there is a hundred this is all
Средняя Азия много там ста это это всё
No for everything was in the Russian Empire
Нет за всё было в Российской империи
Georgia was in the Russian Empire
Грузия была в Российской империи Армения
Armenia was in the Russian Empire Azerbaijan
была в Российской империи Азербайджан
was in Russia no Armenia was not don't
был в россий не Армении не было не
make up Armenia was not The province
придумывайте Армении не было Губерния
was Fliska - this is Georgia Georgia
была была флиска - это это Грузия Грузия
was Azerbaijan and Armenia this is all
была Азербайджан и Армения это всё
fliska Georgia Province is correct fliska
флиска Губерния Грузия правильно флис -
is Tbilisi Yes Tiflis is Tbilisi
это Тбилиси Да Тифлис - это Тбилиси в
modern Azerbaijan Armenia was part of the fliska province
флиску губернию входил современный
Well, look even
Азербайджан Армения Ну смотрите даже
Okay, let it be it was still
Ладно пускай будет она всё равно
restored within the borders
восстановилась в тех границах
that existed
которые существовала
Poland without Finland and Poland already at
Польше без Финляндии и Польши уже как
least Yes, yes and without a part  Ukraine
минимум Да вот да и бе без части Украины
And then you captured a little bit and then
А потом вы захватили чуть-чуть а потом
it came back, everything a little bit and then
она вернулось же всё чучуть да потом
look what came back Well,
смотрите чу кото о вернулось Ну всё
anyway, look, it's called
равно это смотрите это называется
shaking tore up less tore up and so
шатание разорвали меньше разорвали и так
on further In the ninety-first
дальше дальше В девяносто первом
year in Perm it
году в де Перм году ещё больше
fell apart even more Yes after that May swayed a little
развалилось Да после этого немножко май
from it you returned Belarus to your Orbit
от ней качнулся вы вернули в свою Орбиту
Yes out of all 15 republics only
Беларусь Да из всех 15 республик только
Belarus was able to hold on Yes and now there
Беларусь смогли удержать Да и сейчас
will be a second third jerk you  they will tear apart
будет второй третий рывок вас разорвут
Look at the
Смотрите по
national borders by ethnic by
национальным границам по этническим по
religious yes borders what do you think is it
религиозным да границам вы как думаете
on purpose or by accident that you have
специально или случайно навоз вам
so many Islamist migrants in the country
столько мигрантов исламистов в страну
No it is not by accident here no one
Нет не случайно тут никто в этом не
doubts this right And who is this that is
сомневается правильно А кто это
bringing America migrants how the United States of
навозиш Америки как Соединённые Штаты
America is bringing you migrants it
Америки завозят вам мигрантов это Путин
turns out that Putin is bringing them  why Putin to the States What is the
получается почему Путин на штаты Причём
connection here What again who is bringing in
тут связь Какая ещё раз кто завозит
Tajiks Uzbeks all sorts of Kazakhs Kyrgyz
таджиков узбеков всяких казахов кыргызов
Yes, he is bringing in to
Да заводит завозит в
Russia Well, I just answered you The
Россию Ну я же вам ответил только что
United States under the auspices Well, in the
Соединённые Штаты под содействием Ну в
auspices of the United States And what does she
содействие Соединённых Штатов А чем она
do with it These are your officials your laws oh
сове Это ваши чиновники ваши законы о
my god  Let's not touch the officials here, they are so
бог мой Вот тут чиновников Давайте не
corrupt
будем трогать это ж продажная такая та
that they don't
что не дай
God willing, I understand correctly that the States
Бог я правильно понимаю что штаты
bribed Putin so that he would get
подкупили Путина чтобы он
involved, but explain it to me. Why should I
завозился а Ну объясните Ну почему вам
explain it to you? You are talking nonsense. Why
объяснять вы говорите глупости А почему
should I explain nonsense? Well, explain it to me.
я должен глупости объяснять Ну объясните
Look, who is responsible for the situation in
Смотри кто ответственный за ситуацию в
Russia? Putin.
России Путин
And in general, yes, yes, who is responsible then?
А в целом-то да да кто тогда кто отве
Well,  yes, who really don't understand what
Ну да которые реально не понимают что
they're doing. That's who's responsible at the lowest level.
творят Вот кто ответо низшим уровнем да
Well, who appoints these officials at the
Ну а кто назначает этих чиновников
lowest level, who's responsible for them.
низшим уровнем кто за них
Well, that's already how to say it,
ответственный Ну это уже эти как сказать
we have it like in Russia, it's
там у нас как в России идёт
multifunctional. Well, it's stupid to
многофункционально Ну глупо сейчас
say that now. Of course. Okay, but Putin definitely
сказал Конечно Ладно но Путин точно их
doesn't have them.  appoints So who appoints the top
не назначает Так кто назначает верхушку
of the FSB the top of the police the top of the
ээ ФСБ верхушку полиции верхушку
Investigative Committee who Well it's Putin
следственного комитета кто Ну это Путин
of course Putin yes that is it turns out
конечно Путин да то есть получается
Putin is responsible for the work of all
Путин ответственный за работу всех
law enforcement
правоохранительных
agencies Well wait responsible for the
органов Ну подождите ответственно за
law enforcement agencies those
правоохранительных оганов отвечает тех
whom he appointed are responsible so if he appointed
кого он назначил так если он назначил
people who for some reason close  eyes
людей которые почему-то закрывают глаза
on migrants or vice versa promotes
на мигрантов или наоборот способствует
means either he is in the subject or he is about
значит либо он в теме либо он про
Yes here I completely agree with you
Да вот тут я с вами полностью согласен
but decrees are issued that promote
но издаются указы которые способствуют
implementation from the highest to the lowest level and
выполнению с высшего на низший уровень и
which the lowest level does not understand them
который низший уровень их не понимаете
You  you yourself understand perfectly well that the
Вы же сами прекрасно понимаете что
lowest level Well, people who are
низший уровень Ну люди которые
subject to corruption of all the other
подвержены коррупции всей остальной
nonsense money
ерунды денежка
plays correctly And why doesn't the one who sits at
играет правильно А почему тот кто сидит
the top do tough purges of those
наверху не делает жёсткие чистки тех
corrupt officials and so on Then he is
коррупционеров и так Дальше он же
responsible And do you know how many
ответствен А вы знаете у нас уже сколько
purges have already happened to us A nightmare as far as you are not
чисток произошло Кошмар на сколько вы не
in  course No
в курсе Нет А
Why I don't know First time I hear Tell me
почему не знаю Впервые слышу Расскажите
Yes I won't tell you you
Да я что не буду вам рассказывать вы
Open the Russian press and read the
Откройте российскую прессу и читайте
purges are happening completely he
чистки происходят полностью он
Ministry of Defense What purges
Министерство обороне Какие чистки
are happening correctly
происходят правильно
What purges are happening and the nightmarish ones
Какие чистки происходят а кошмарные Вот
Look how Trump Trump really said
смотри как Трамп Трамп реально сказал
everything they banned migrants they send everyone
всё запретили мигрантам высылают всех
straight away  in batches Yes, they closed the border, and
прямо пачками Да закрыли границу а у
you, and we, Russia, are also sending in
васс а у нас России отправляют тоже
batches no no yes how No, last
пачками нет нет да как Нет за прошлый
year, last year, 200 people were deported
год за прошлый год депортированы 200
only Yes no no Don't
человек только Да не не Вот вы не
make things up, I read it, I Open it now,
придумывайте я читал я Откройте сейчас
you have a computer, look,
вот у вас компьютер есть вот посмотрите
even I  this is such a distant person I know
даже я вот такой далёкий человек Я знаю
that at least 20 still And why
что не менее 20 до сих пор А почему
then Russia still hasn't made
Россия тогда до сих пор не сделала с
this visa regime with Tajikistan even
таджикистаном этот визовый режим даже
Turkey did
Турция сделала
A I don't know I can't answer you
А я не знаю я не могу Вам ответить на
this question it's just Putin said that they would
этот вопрос это ж просто Путин сказал бы
have made a visa regime tomorrow
так сделали визовый режим завтра бы
Well how do I know You T are
сделали Ну я откуда я знаю Вы Т меня
asking me what I am Putin that is Putin
спрашиваете что я Путин то есть Путин
turns out to be in the topic of bringing foreigners into the
получается в теме завоза иностранцев в
Russian Federation
Российскую Федерацию
not just foreigners
не просто иностранцев
but representatives of radical
а представителей радикального
Islamism to distort words just in
исламизма передёргивать слова просто в
this book just Yes, here just there is
этой книжке как раз Да тут как раз есть
a chapter You see in the book you can describe
глава Понимаете в книжке можно описать
anything It is very
что угодно Тут очень
interesting to take here swear no
интересно брать руга нет
azhan nira
ажа нира
brothers Strugatsky this is the same you can say
братья стругацки это же можно сказать
Semino famous writers now I
семино известные писатели сейчас я
by the way I now  I'll look at the number of
кстати я сейчас посмотрю количество
passports issued to Tajiks now,
паспортов выданных таджикам было сейчас
let's go, let's take a look.
давайте давайте да посмотрите Вот видите
You see what kind of
вы какой
mobile phone I'm just curious, I'm a
мобильный я просто вот интересно
Slav. Well, of course, this is a controversial issue.
славянин Ну это конечно спорный вопрос
But it doesn't matter. You're
Но неважно вы
blaming Ukraine and sitting under the
скате всё с Украиной и сидите под флагом
American flag. Look, in the second year.
Америки вот смотрите в д втором году
Look, in the third year.
смотрите вот в д третьем году Российская
378,000 people from the Central
378.000 человек из республик Средней
Asian republics received Russian citizenship. So what? 3 million in
Азии вот Ну и что 3 миллиона только в
2023 alone. You only have 3 million.
двадцать третьем году только 3 милна у
Well, well, well, what next? Everything is
вас Ну ну Ну дальше что Всё всё
fine if for this. And how much?
нормально если для это А сколько
deportation was You look
депортива было Вы посмотрите давайте
let's look now
давайте сейчас посмотрим
this is on legal grounds
это ж на законных основаниях получили
people received citizenship so this is 300,000 these are those
люди гражданство так это 300.000 это те
who received citizenship what
которые получили гражданство какая
difference does it make now
разница сейчас
like
вот
this twenty-fourth year yes the number of
так двадцать четвёртый год да число
migrants deported from Russia
депортированных из России мигрантов
has fallen and is 12 12273
упало и составляет 12 12273
people and where are you looking
человека а где вы смотрите
Well here  site
Ну вот сайт
Ifa yes it turns out Well it turns out it's one
Ифа да получается Ну получается это один
train well 20
поезд ну 20
pla understood And the question is don't you think
пла понял А вопрос такой вам не кажется
that in Russia there is some kind of
что в России идёт какой-то такой
special process of pumping Chechnya
специальный процесс накачки Чечни
with weapons yes that is
оружием да то есть
huge weapons a huge number of
огромное вооружение огромное количество
fighters there who are not fighting anywhere yes that
там бойцов которые нигде не воюют да то
is this circus  Akhmat TikTok troops they are
есть этот цирк Ахмат тикток войска они
taking pictures everywhere Yes but for
всюду там фотографируются Да но
some reason there are no dead or wounded Chechens
почему-то погибших и раненых чеченцев
Russian guys are dying
нету русские парни погибают
Yes and the Chechens are training the Chechens
Да а чеченцы тренируются чеченцы
are getting ready the Chechens are arming themselves Why do
готовятся чеченцы вооружаются Почему так
n't you
не
say that I won't say I
скажете я не скажу я
know how you feel about this
зна а как вы к этому
I know about the fact that I don't  I know very
относитесь зна отно к тому что я не знаю
well how you feel about
хорошо как вы вообще относитесь к
Ramzan
Рамзану
Kadyrov
Кадырову
as the head of the Republic  Russian
как глава Республики Российской
Federation Hero of Russia
Федерации Герой России вопрос
you asked me a question
задали вы мне вопрос задали
Yes I answered you you are the first Russian
Да я вам ответил вы первый россиянин
who admitted that Ramzan Kadyrov Chen chem
который признался что Рамзан Кадыров Чен
respect What does respect have to do with it It's a pity that
почтение Причём тут почтение Жалко что в
next time we won't be able to talk to you
следующий раз не сможем с вами
Why Because
Почему Потому что
Schwab These are your wet thoughts well look
Шваб Это ваши влажные мысли ну смотрите
You  citizen of the Russian Federation Yes, you
Вы гражданин Российской Федерации Да
publicly
публично
call an official Hero of Russia
называете должностное лицо Героя России
official Lio official Chen
должностное Лио чиновника Чен
on this on a representative of the state
на это на представителя государственной
power of the Russian Federation this is a
власти Российской Федерации это
criminal criminal act criminally
криминально уголовное деяние уголовно
punishable No no this is my personal
наказуемое Нет нет это моё личное
opinion Well your personal opinion is
мнение Ну Ваше личное мнение есть
slander against Ramzan Akhmatovich Kadyrov
клеветой на Рамзан ахматовича Кадырова
No this you now want to turn over
Нет это Вы сейчас хотите перевернуть то
what I said there is no need to invent it well
что я сказал не надо придумывать хорошо
Explain why then you call
Объясните почему тогда вы называете
Ramzan Kadyrov not a hug to you here
Рамзана Кадырова не бу обнять вам вот
I will not explain to you I am
вам я не буду объяснять я
good And then how does it turn out that
хорошо А тогда как получается что
Putin is the Guarantor of the Constitution there the Supreme
Путин Гарант Конституции там Верховный
Commander-in-Chief then appointed a
главнокомандующий дальше назначил
Chechen as the head of the
чеченского главой
Republic these are not questions for me as you  How do you
Республики это не ко мне вопросы как вы
feel about this as a citizen? I'll
как гражданин к этому относитесь я ещё
say again how can I feel about this?
раз говорю как я могу относиться к тому
which I didn't
чего я не
do But it was done in your country love go
делал Но это сделали в вашей стране лове
Okay let me ask you a river
подите Хорошо давайте я вам речный
question let's say you know who
вопрос задам давайте вы знаете кто такой
Oles Buzina is Oles Buzina I know yes And why did they
олес бузина олес бузина знаю да А почему
kill him because he
его убили потому что
was
был
pro-Russian I understand everything And why did they
пророссийский Всё понял А почему про
kill the pro-Russian ones also then they
российским грохнули также киву потом
killed Kiva like in Russia everything Dasha Dugi everything
грохнули типа в России всё Дашу дуги всё
yes
да
everything and why did they want you in a free country
все а почему вас в свободной стране
look we Like a Cossack spirit
захотели смотрите мы Як козацького духу
such a guy Yes we have the EU Yes Ukraine
такого хлопци Да у нас так ЕС Да Украина
Yes we are Cossacks Rus' where Damn Cossacks
Да казаки мы Русь откуда Блин казаки
took so that's what we did Ukraine
взяли так вот и что мы сделали Украине
got Cossacks Now explain to me
взялись казаки Вот вот поясните мне
please come from Poland and the Polish
пожалуйста из Польши пришли а польские
Cossacks that is Polish women Yes Polish Kazakhs
казаки то есть польки Да польские казах
came here I will
прили
interrupt you We have Moscow
вот вас перебью У нас есть московские
Cossacks also Just like Ukrainian
казаки ещё Во так же как и украинские
Cossacks Here is how Ukraine differs
казаки У нас вот чем отличается Украина
from Russia look in Ukraine there are such as
от России смотрите в Украине э такие как
Oles Buzina who is against Ukraine and
Олесь Бузина который против Украины и
Ukrainians Yes, and in Russia those who are
украинцев Да его ж а в России те которые
against Russians Like Ramzan Kadyrov Yes, he is a
против русских Как Рамзан Кадыров Да он
hero of Russia, everyone kisses his
герой России ему все целуют короче
boots, in short Why is it
сапоги Почему
so
так заезде
interesting
интересный был
character was a developed man We are still
персонаж разви сний мужик Мы тебя ещё
right there eye spinning
прямо глаз крутится
Kadyrovites are already
ему кадыровцы уже этот Интернет
turning off this Internet now
отключают сейчас
everything is like a squeak comment this is good
всё так лайк писка комент це хорошая
Roma was subscribe to my Telegram
ромова была пидпишить на мий Telegram
right now axis win and
прямо зараз ось вин а
Popik this is very and very important YouTube
Попик це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
driving us through scarg ORV yours  ban and
загоняя нас через скарг ОРВ твый бан и
very many videos I don't show to people sometimes I
дуже багато вдео не показую людям вчасно
don't show information about streams That's
не показуе информация про стрими Тому
why we Mali operational links
для того щоб ми Мали оперативний звязок
are written right now and while there are videos in telegram
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okm there are also interesting and useful
окм видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we are responsible for the latest
информация и мы повинни ва трима постный
operational links regardless of
оперативный звязок незалежно
what we show  you about this YouTube Glory to
того чи покаже вам про це YouTube Слава
Ukraine subscribe
Украине подпишись